Guide to the Time Inc. Fortune Publishing and Business Records 1929-2005 MS 3009-RG 25
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1978-2005; 32 Linear feet in 32 record cartons
  - Subseries V.C. Fortune Week, 1993-1994; 6.5 Linear feet in 7 record cartons
    - 1994 May 6 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 5-6-94".
    - 1994 May 13 (Offsite-box 2933, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 5-13-94".
    - 1994 May 17 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 5-17-94".
    - 1994 May 27 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 5-27-94".
    - 1994 May 27 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 5-27-94".
    - 1994 June 3 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 6-3-94".
    - 1994 Jun 4, 1994 June 4 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 6-4-94".
    - 1994 June 18 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case: "Fortune Week 6/18/94". On label on cassette: "FW 6/18".
    - 1994 June 25 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case: "Fortune Week 6-25-94". On labe on cassette: "FW 6/25".
    - 1994 July 2 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case: "Fortune Week 7/2/94". On label on cassette: "FW 7/2".
    - 1994 July 9 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 7/9/94".
    - 1994 July 15 (Offsite-box 2934, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Fortune Week 7-15-94".
    - 1994 July 22 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 7-22-94".
    - 1994 July 29 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 7-29-94".
    - 1994 August 6 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Fortune Week 8-6-94".
    - 1994 August 12 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Fortune Week 8-12-94".
    - 1994 August 19 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Fortune Week 8/19/94 Geoff Colvin Hosts". On label on case side: "Fortune Week 8/20/94 Terence Pare".
    - 1994 August 26 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Geoff Colvin Hosts". On labels on case side and cassette: "Fortune Week 8/26/94". Includes a note which says: "David Kirkpatrick".
    - 1994 September 2 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 9/2/94".
    - 1994 September 10 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 9/10/94".
    - 1994 September 16 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Fortune Week 9-16-94".
    - 1994 September 23 (Offsite-box 2935, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Fortune Week 9/23/94 Peter Petre". On labels on case side and cassette: "Fortune Week 9/23/94".
    - 1994 October 1 (Offsite-box 2936, Item 1)
      Separated Materials
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Fortune Week 10-1-94".
    - 1994 October 8 (Offsite-box 2936, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Week 10/8/94".
    - 1994 October 21, 1994 October 94 (Offsite-box 2936, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "Fortune Week 10-21-94".
  - Subseries V.D. Wall Street Week with Fortune, 2002-2003; .5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Originally launched as Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser in 1972, the show ran under this name from 1972 to 2002. During a revamp in 2002, original host, Louis Rukeyser, was replaced in an attempt to attract a younger audience. Relaunched as Wall Street Week with Fortune, it was now a joint venture between Fortune, Maryland Public Television, and PBS. The new hosts of the show were Geoffrey Colvin, the editorial director of Fortune, and Karen Gibbs, who was previously a senior business correspondent for Fox News. The host, along with panelists, would discuss financial markets, the economy, and financial issues in an attempt to help keep investors informed about developments. Despite attempts to grow the audience, the show was canceled in 2005.
    Ives, Nat. "'Wall St. Week,' a PBS Staple, Will Go Off the Air in June." The New York Times. March 24, 2005. Accessed January 04, 2019. https://www.nytimes.com/2005/03/24/business/media/wall-st-week-a-pbs-staple-will-go-off-the-air-in-june.html
    "Wall $treet Week with Fortune." IMDb. Accessed January 04, 2019. https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0346443/
    "Wall $treet Week with Louis Rukeyser." IMDb. Accessed January 04, 2019. https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0255766/
    The Wall Street Week with Fortune subseries contains materials from 2002 to 2003. Included in the subseries are videotapes with recordings of episodes of the show.
    - #0108, 2002 August 16 (Offsite-box 2936, Item 4)
      1 videocassete (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on cassette: "Wall Street Week with Fortune 08/16/02-#0108".
    - #0108, 2002 August 16 (Offsite-box 2936, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on cassette: "WallStreet Week with Fortune 08/16/02-#0108".
    - Underwriting Sales Reel, 2003 March 19 (Offsite-box 2936, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (2 min., 36 sec.): 1/2 in. On labels on cassette: "Wall Street Week with Fortune 3/19/03 Underwriting Sales Reel trt: 2:36".
    - Underwriting Sales Reel, 2003 March 19 (Offsite-box 2936, Item 7)
    - National Underwriting Credit Reel, undated (Offsite-box 2936, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label on cassette front: "Wall Street Week with Fortune Nat'l UW Credit Reel". On label on cassette side: "Wall Street Week with Fortune National Underwriting Credit Reel Date?".
  - Subseries V.E. Miscellaneous, 1978-2004; 5.7 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
    The Miscellaneous subseries contains materials from 1978 to 2004 and include recordings of employee interviews, events, seminars, ads, training and orientation videos, and mentions of Fortune in the media. These recordings are mainly on U-matic and VHS cassettes but Betacam and Betamax cassettes are also included as well as open reel audiotapes.
    - Fortune New Bi-Weekly Staff Interviews, 1978 January 6 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (20 min.): 1/2 in. On label on case side: "#66 Fortune - new bi-weekly staff interviews 1/6/1978". On label on cassette: "#66 Time In. Archives".
    - Fortune New Bi-Weekly Staff Interviews, 1978 January 6 (Offsite-box 2938, Folder 1)
      Originally enclosed with Fortune New Bi-Weekly Staff Interviews, Box 2938 Item 1. Folder includes a description of the video.
    - Fortune 50th Anniversary, 1980 March 18 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 2)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Written on box cover: "Speed 7 1/2 IPS Reel music date? Fortune 50th Anniversary". Written on box side: "Fortune 50 Anniv 3/18/1980". Written inside the box: "1. Green Eyes 2. You made me love you 3. Long ago and far away 4. That old black magic 5. You'd be so nice to come home to 6. Tico-Tico 7. 8. Sugar Blues 9. Where or when 10. You were meant for me 11. Tammy".
    - Fortune 50th Anniversary, 1980 March 18 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 3)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Written on box cover: "Speed 7 1/2 IPS Reel music date? Fortune 50th Anniversary". Written on box side: "Fortune 50 Anniv music 3/18/1980". Written inside the box: "1. It's Delovely 2. Lovely to look at 3. Ru, and Coca-Cola 4. The devil and the deep blue sea 5. You belong to me 6. C'est si bon 7. witchcraft 8. You were meant for me 9. Nice work if you can get it 10. Interme220".
    - Fortune's 50th Anniversary Show: Song Excerpts, 1980 March 18 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic)(30 min): On label on case front: "'Fortune's 50th Anniversary Show Song Excerpts 3/18/80". On label on case side: "'Fortune S 50th Anniversary Show' Song Excerpts 3/1980". On label on cassette front: " "Fortune's 50th Anniversary Show" Song Excerpts 3/18/80". On label on cassette side: "30 min".
    - Fortune Magazine 50th Anniversary, 1980 April 10 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (small Betamax)(1 hr): On cassette label: "Fortune Magazine '50th Anniversary' 1 hour DUB 4/10/80 X1".
    - Fortune Magazine 50th Anniversary, 1980 April 10 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (small Betamax) (1 hr): On cassette label: "small beta Fortune Magazine '50th Anniversary' 1 Hour DUB 4/10/80 X2".
    - Stan Freberg: Federal Budget Revue, 1980 October 2 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (30 min): On labels on case front and cassette: "Title: Stan Freberg Federal Budget Revue Rev. Rev. Rev. 10/2/80 Minutes: 30 FBR-25 3rd Revision". On label on case side: "Title: Stan Freberg Federal Budget Revue Rev.Rev.Rev. 10/2/80 Minutes: 30". Includes a sticker on case side: "30".
    - Fortune: Weeden, Finkle, Fay Musical: Today Show: WNBC, 1982 November 18 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case: "Fortune - Weeden, Finkle, Fay Musical Today Show - WNBC 11/19/82".
    - Fortune Sales Conference: Seabrook Island Resort, 1983 September 11-15 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrok Island Resort September 11-15, 1983 Marketing: Introductionn Howard Kaplan Director of Marketing Research: Gail Clyma Director of Marketing Research Simmons- Gail Clyma ORC- Libbie Foote Wall Street Journal Study- Fred Trautmann Public Activities Analysis- Lori Sturn Personal Financial Services- Jack Belknap Belnap Data Solutions". On sticker on case front: "Tape #1". On label on case side: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook 9/11-15/1983 Tape #1".
    - Fortune Sales Conference: Seabrook Island Resort, 1983 September 11-15 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook Island Resort September 11-15, 1983 Research: continued Conclusion- Jack Belknap Internation Research- Ann Scholl/Gail Clyma Promotion: David Nimz Promotion Director Edit Presentation- Sue Ognibene New Promotional Tools- David Nimz Merchandising/Sales Support- Etta Olmsted Consumer Presentation- Chuck Jennes". On sticker on case front: "Tape #2". On label on case side: "Fortune Sales Conf. 9/11-15/1983 Tape #2".
    - Fortune Sales Conference: Seabrook Island Resort, 1983 September 14 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook Island Resort September 11-15, 1983 Tape #3 September 14, 1983 1. Fortune Competition A.J. Cusick (1) Cusick and Richardson/Arnold vs. Business Week 2. "Fortune vs. Forbes" Jack Haire James Graham 3. "Fortune vs. Wall Street Journal" Peter Scull Bruce Brandfon 4. "Fortune vs. TV" E. William Kenyon William McMurray". On label on case side: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook 9/14/1983 Tape #3". On label on cassette: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook Island Resort September 11-15, 1983 September 14, 1983 Fortune Competition A.J. Cusick ""Fortune vs. Business Week" Jack Haire James Graham "Fortune vs. Wall Street Journal" Peter Scull Bruce Brandfon "Fortune vs. TV E. William Kenyon William McMurray".
    - Fortune Sales Conference: Seabrook Island Resort, 1983 September 14 (Offsite-box 2938, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook Island Resort September 11-15, 1983 September 14, 1983 Tape 4. "Fortune vs. TV", Cont. "The New Fortune Agency Presentation" Bruce McNaughton "Fiscal Fitness" James B. Hoefer". On label on case side: "Seabrook Sales Meeting - 9/83 1. The New Fortune Agency Presentation (McNaughton) 2. Fiscal Fitness (Hoefer) (Tape #4)". On label on cassette: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook Island Resort September 11-15, 1983 September 14, 1983 "Fortune vs. TV", Cont. "The New Fortune Agency Presentation" Bruce McNaughton "Fiscal Fitness" James B. Hoefer".
    - Fortune Sales Conference: Seabrook Island Resort, 1983 September 14 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Tape B Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook Island Resort September 11-15, 1983 September 14, 1983 Fortune International Bruce Barnet Thomas Curtin Michael Dudler Special Sections: U.S. Allan Shubert Joe Dillon Fran Hall". On label on case side: "Seabrook Sales Meeting - 9/83 1. Fortune Int'l (Barnet, Curtin, Dudler) 2. Special Sections (Shubert, Hall, Dillon)." On label on cassette: "Fortune Sales Conference Seabrook Island Resort September 11-15, 1983 September 14, 1983 Fortune International Bruce Barnet Thomas Curtin Michael Dudler Special Sections: U.S. Allan Shubert Joe Dillon Fran Hall".
    - Fortune: Weeden, Finkle, and Fay: Seabrook Island Resort, 1983 October 19 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (12 min.): On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Weeden, Finkle, and Fay Seabrook Island Resort 12:00 Approx. 10/19/83". On label on case side: "Weeden, Finkle and Fay Seabrook Sales Meeting - 10/19/83".
    - Good News and Fiscal Fitness, 1983 November 11 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Magazine "Good News" 1:37 11/11/83 Weeden, Finkle and Fay "Fiscal Fitness" WTBS". On label on case side: "Fortune Good News 11/11/83".
    - Required Entertainment for the Business Class, 1984 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front and cassette: "Required Entertainment for the Business Class Fortune 1984 Weeden, Finkle and Fay". On label on case side: "Weeden, Finkle and Fay Required Entertainment for the Business Class - 1984".
    - KUP's Show: Rukeyser, Searingen, Pritzker, Jorgensen, 1984 March 23 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (57 min., 50 sec.): On label on case front: "Series Title KUP's Show Program Title Rukeyser, Searingen, Pritzker, Jorgensen Cassette Length 60:00 Program Length 57:50 Record Date 3-23-84". On label on case side: "KUP's Show Series Title Rukeyser Program Title 3-23-84 Records Date". On label on cassette: "Series Title KUP's Show Rukeyser, Swearingen, Pritzker, Jorgensen Cassette Length 60:00 Program Length 57:50 Record Date 3-23-84".
    - 1985 Sales Conference: Weeden, Finkle and Fay, 1985 September 13 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Tape 1 Weeden Finkle and Fay 1985 Sales Conf 9/13/85". On label on case side: "Weeden, Finkle and Fay 1985 Sales Meeting - September 13, 1985". On label on cassette: "Weeden Finkle and Fay 1985 Sales Fortune".
    - Fortune: The 25th Anniversary Japanese Section, 1986 March 21 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune "The 25th Anniversary Japanese Section" 3/21/86".
    - Fortune Magazine: Retirement Luncheon: 21 Club, 1987 June 17 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case side: "Fortune Retirement Luncheon 6/17/1987 "21" Club (1) (#1)". On label on cassette: "Fortune Magazine Retirement Luncheon June 17, 1987 "21" Club Tape #1".
    - Fortune Magazine: Retirement Luncheon: 21 Club, 1987 June 17 (Offsite-box 2937, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case side: "Fortune Ret. Lunch 6/17/87 (2)". On label on cassette: "Fortune Magazine Retirement Luncheon June 17, 1987 "21" Club Tape #2".
    - Weeden, Finkel, and Fay: Fortune: "Sexy", 1987 December 4 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (40 min.): 1/2 in. On label on case front: "Weeden, Finkel and Fay Fortune "Sexy" 12/4/87 40:00". On label on case side: "Fortune Weeden, Finkel, and Fay "Sexy" 12/4/1987". On label on cassette: "Weeden, Finkel and Fay Fortune "Sexy" 12/4/87 40:00 12/14/87".
    - Fortune: The World of Business, 1988 January (Offsite-box 2939, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (15 min.): On labels on case and cassette front: "Fortune The World of Business January 1988". On label on cassette side: "15min".
    - Fortune: Faces, 1988 June 22 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (4 min., 50 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune "Faces" 4:50 6/22/88". On label on case side: "Fortune "Faces" 6/22/88".
    - Fortune Magazine: Vaya Con Dios Whitey, 1988 November 16 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (4 min., 22 sec.): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Magazine Presents "Vaya Con Dios Whitey". On label on case side: "Vaya Con Dios Whitey 11/16/88".
    - Fortune Magazine: Fortune 500: You're the Top, 1988 November 22 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (2 min., 30 sec.): 1/2 in. On label on cassette side: "Fortune Magazine Fortune 500 "You're the Top" 11/2/88 2:30". Label on cassette back: [illegible].
    - Exxon and Fortune Magazine Mention: Tonight Show: NBC, 1989 April 19 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 10 sec.): On label on case front and cassette: "'Exxon and Fortune Magazine Mention' Tonight Show 4/19/89, NBC, 11:30pm, (3:10)". On label on case side: "Fortune and Exxon mention 4/18/1989 NBC 1130p Tonight Show".
    - Fortune: Image Television Spots, 1989 September 7 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min.): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "D.Nimz Date: September 7, 1989 Title: Fortune - Image Television Spots Time: 3 Minutes 00 seconds STD: 625 Lines PAL U-matic STDS. Conversion Client: Fortune Magazine". On label on case side: "Fortune Image Television Spots 9/7/1989". On label on cassette: "Date: September 7, 1989 Title: Fortune - Image Television Spots Time: 3 Minutes 00 seconds STD: 625 Lines PAL U-matic STDS. Conversion Client: Fortune Magazine".
    - Masthead: The People of Time Inc. Magazines, 1989 September 19 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case and cassette: "Masthead: The People of Time Inc. Magazines".
    - Masthead: The People of Time Inc. Magazines, 1989 September 19 (Offsite-box 2939, Folder 1)
      The folder contains a letter sent Jane Cummins to Kathi Doak concerning the tape "Masthead: The People of Time Inc. Magazines" which was used for orientation of new employees. The letter is dated September 19, 1989. This letter was originally housed with Box 2939 Item 8.
    - Images of Fortune: A Celebration of 60 Years: International, 1990 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "-International- Images of Fortune A Celebration of 60 Years". On label on case side: "Fortune 60 Anniv. 1990".
    - Fortune 60th Anniversary, 1990 February 20 (Offsite-box 2940, Item 1)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 15 ips; 10 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. Written on box side: "1 2/20/90". Written on box back: "Michael Feinstein Feb. 20, 1990 Mark Hopkins Hotel San Francisco Fortune 60th Anniv. 4 tok TASCAM 34-B 15 ips no noise reducton 1khz tone at odb vu ch. 1 - vox ch 2. - piano low ch. 3. - piano high/podium ch 4 - audience Tails Out Reel #1". On label on reel: "AMPEX 456".
    - Fortune 60th Anniversary, 1990 February 20 (Offsite-box 2940, Item 2)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 15 ips; 10 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. Written on box side: "2 2/20/90". Written on box back: "Michae; Feinstien Feb. 20, 1990 Mark Hopkans Hotel San Francisco Fortune 60th Anniv. 4 trk. TASCAM 34 B 15 ips no noise reduction see head of reel #1 for reference time ch 1- Vox ch 2- piano low ch 3- piano hi/podium ch 4- audience Tails Out Reel #2".
    - Fortune 60th Anniversary, 1990 February 20 (Offsite-box 2940, Item 3)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 15 ips; 10 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. Written on box side: "3 2/20/90". Written on box back: "Michael Feinstein Feb 20, 1990 Mak Hopkis Hotel San Francisco Fortune 60th Anniv. 4 trk TASCAM 34B 15 ips no noise reduction 1kHz ref at odb vu at Tail ch1 - Vox ch2 - piano low ch3 - piano hi/podium ch4 - audience Tails Out Reel #3".
    - Fortune 60th Anniversary, 1990 February 20 (Offsite-box 2940, Item 4)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 15 ips, stereo; 10 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. tape. Written on box front: "I". Written on box side: "I 2/20/90". Written on box back: "Micheal Feinstein Feb 20, 1990 Mark Hopkins Hotel San Francisco Fortune 60th Anniversary 2tk stereo master no reduction 15ips +3/250 nWb [illegible] 1k, 10k at Ovu at Head Tails Out Reel I mixer: Bob Stander".
    - Fortune 60th Anniversary, 1990 February 20 (Offsite-box 2940, Item 5)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 15 ips, stereo; 10 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. Written on box front: "II". Written on box side: "II 2/20/90". Written on box back: "Michael Feinstein 2/20/90 S.F., Ca. Fortune 60th Anniversary 2tk stereo Master 15ips No Reduction +3/250 Tones on Reel I Tails Out Reel II".
    - Fortune 60th Anniversary, 1990 February 20 (Offsite-box 2940, Item 6)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 15 ips, stereo; 10 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. Written on box front: "III". Written on box side: "III 2/20/90". Writtem on box back: "Michael Feinstein 2/20/90 S.F. CA. Fortune 60th Anniversary 2tk stereo master 15ips novr +3/250 nWbhm Tones on Reel I Tails Out Reel III".
    - Fortune Media Presentation, 1990 November 28 (Offsite-box 2939, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (8 min.): On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune "Fortune Media Presentation" 8:00 11/28/90". On label on case side: "Fortune Media Presentation 1990".
    - Time Warner Overview: Generic Version, 1991 May (Offsite-box 2939, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Time Warner Overview Generic Version May 1991".
    - Time Warner Overview: Generic Version, 1991 May (Offsite-box 2939, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case and cassette: "Time Warner Overview Generic Version May 1991".
    - Fortune Presentation Video, 1991 November 6 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min.): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Presentation Video 11/6/91 3:00 MASTER". On label on case side: "Fortune Presentation Video 11/6/91 3:00".
    - Fortune Magazine: Minds Campaign Video, 1991 November 20 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "What is smart management really all about? It's about teamwork, leadership, attitude, recruitment. This special behind-the-scenes video will show you what Fortune journalists learn about these qualities when they go "inside the mind of managemnet." Fortune Insie the mind of management". On label on case side: "Fortune "Minds Campaign Video" 11/20/1991". On label on cassette front: "Fortune Magazine Minds Campaign Video 11/20/91 not for commercial use". On label on cassette side: "Maxima Magnetics C and E 11423-0606".
    - Fortune Perot Poll: Tonight Show, 1992 June 9 (Offsite-box 2941, Item 3)